<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="questions">
        <item>What is launcher?</item>
        <item>What is icon pack?</item>
        <item>How to use icon pack?</item>
        <item>How to apply icon pack?</item>
        <item>How to see all icons included?</item>
        <item>I can\'t see icon name completely</item>
        <item>How to replace icon with alternate icon?</item>
        <item>How to request icon?</item>
        <item>How to restore remaining Premium Request after reinstalling icon pack?</item>
        <item>After restarting my phone, icon pack not applied, it restore to default?</item>
        <item>Why icons looks jaggy or pixelated on my phone?</item>
        <item>I can see the icon inside all icons included,
            but why the actual icon on app drawer still not changed?</item>
        <item>What is report bugs?</item>
        <item>My launcher listed on google play description, but why it\'s not included in apply section?</item>
        <item>Wallpaper can\'t be applied, just showing black screen?</item>
        <item>Muzei: How to load downloaded wallpaper only?</item>
        <item>Muzei: I don\'t want to keep downloading wallpaper each time wallpaper change?</item>
        <item>Muzei: I only want to use several wallpaper?</item>
        <item>Why WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE &amp; READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why INTERNET permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why ACCESS_WIFI_STATE permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why SET_WALLPAPER permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why SET_WALLPAPER_HINTS permission needed?</item>
        <item>Why WAKE_LOCK Permission needed?</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="answers">
        <item>Launcher is part of the Android user interface that lets users customize the home screen,
            launch mobile apps, make phone calls, and perform other tasks on Android devices.</item>
        <item>A set of graphics that will change the look of your app drawer icons.</item>
        <item>You will need a launcher that support Icon Pack.
            You can see on Google Play Store description for supported launcher.
            If you confused which launcher should be used, just go to \"Apply\" section, then install from there.</item>
        <item>You can open navigation drawer (slide from left corner to right) then open \"Apply\".
            Choose which launcher that you used.
            If your launcher not listed there but this icon pack compatible with that
            (see on Google Play Store description for supported launcher),
            you can apply it manually from launcher settings.</item>
        <item>You can open navigation drawer (slide from left corner to right) then open \"Icons\".</item>
        <item>Just tap on icon, preview dialog will appear shown bigger image and icon name completely.</item>
       	<item>It depends what launcher did you used. Not every launcher support icon editing.
       	    Mostly you can edit icon by tap &amp; hold icon or double tap icon.</item>
        <item>You can open navigation drawer (slide from left corner to right) then open \"Icon Request\".</item>
        <item>Open Settings, choose \"Restore Purchases\". If you have remaining Premium Request before reinstalling, it will restored.</item>
        <item>It happened because this icon pack moved to SD Card, you should install this in internal memory.</item>
       	<item>The problem might comes from launcher that you used when handling big resolution.
       	    You can fix it by increasing icon size to 115 - 120%.
       	    Or try to change your launcher.</item>
       	<item>Press options menu (on top right corner or use hardware button on your phone),
       	    then choose \"Report Bugs\".</item>
        <item>\"Report Bugs\" used to report bugs related to icon pack not the dashboard.</item>
      	<item>Not every launcher support direct apply, and some of them can\'t be accessed directly from this dashboard app.
      	    You can apply this icon pack manually from launcher settings.</item>
      	<item>When you \"Set Wallpaper\" directly from dashboard app, wallpaper will be downloaded as a cache,
      	    then dashboard app will trying to apply it. Applying process will takes some time and also need huge amount of RAM.
      	    \"Black Screen\" result might happened because your phone doesn\'t have enough free RAM to process the wallpaper.
      	    Restarting your phone will fix this problem. After restarted, your phone will get more free RAM.
            Alternatively, you can open downloaded wallpaper from your Gallery and set as wallpaper from there.</item>
        <item>Open muzei, choose this icon pack, settings. You will see an option to load downloaded wallpaper only.
            You need to download wallpaper from Dashboard first.</item>
        <item>If wallpaper already downloaded, wallpaper will loaded from your phone memory automatically.
            Muzei won\'t keep downloading it when wallpaper change. You need to download wallpaper from Dashboard first.</item>
        <item>Open Dashboard, download wallpaper that you want to use for Muzei.
            Open Muzei settings, then choose Load Downloaded Wallpaper Only.</item>
        <item>It used to write &amp; read cache, and icon request data.</item>
        <item>It used to load Cloud Based Wallpaper &amp; download it.</item>
        <item>It used to check if your phone has internet connection or not.</item>
        <item>It used to check if your phone has internet connection from wifi or not, to load cloud wallpapers from Muzei.</item>
        <item>It used to apply wallpaper directly from dashboard app.</item>
        <item>It used to adjust wallpaper based on your screen resolution.</item>
        <item>It used by Muzei Live Wallpaper</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
